[{"answer": "Well, you know, when I competed at a very young age with Russians, it was illegal for them to be homosexual.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Because you were appointed by President Obama's administration to go and represent the country and a few days later, you came out, what do you make about this whole issue down there of the way they treat homosexuals?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "When you were asked to go and represent your country, by your President to do this, did you have any qualms at all about going there, knowing what the reception is likely to be?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "OITANO: I would probably say it's a privilege to be here as a guest in your country.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "If you did, what would you say to him?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think that the athletes who go over there, they have a task at hand.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Is it advisable to do that to provoke the beast if you like so publicly?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "You know, I think everybody is worried about security but I do think that it's the first priority.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Are you worried about the athlete security?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "It was difficult.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "On a personal level, coming out at 50, I think it was when you did quite recently I mean how did that feel for you?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, I was pleasantly surprised by the reaction but I wasn't relieved, I wasn't relieved.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "How would you describe it?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "That's a good point because everybody wants to be known their accomplishments and being gay is one aspect of who I am, you know, I am son, I'm a brother, I'm a cook, I'm everything, I'm an athlete.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "... rather than a great American athlete?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "It's pretty amazing and it sort of opened my whole demographic up to a lot younger generation.'", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "It doesn't get better than that, isn't it Brian?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Your new project is called the Boitano Project?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Yeah, it is but I found my great, great grandfather's house in a village where every Boitano came from and I bought it from 20 Boitano's and I renovated it so that I can have my family go there.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "That's kind of a makeover show, is it?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, the act itself like you said it would actually just allow people to carry a firearm without a permit.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Why my name is involved and what you have to achieve?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "... secure that.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What's it got to do with me?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "It's a constitutional right that we have that is in shrine.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "And what is your point about the second amendment?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Look, do you know what this is?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "It's Kinder surprise egg.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Well, it depends.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Would you describe it?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Because the government has interfered and is trying to protect us from ourselves.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Do you know why they're illegal?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, look, I'm not allowed to eat a chocolate egg in America, it's illegal.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Well, what is the irony?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "The federal government has become very ...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "And I can go and buy 2,360 different types of guns?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "It does indeed.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Does that strike you as strange?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "I love the Kinder eggs.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "So you went battleheart (ph) with me to save the Kinder egg for the American people?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Well, this won't flood the streets with more guns.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "What do you think more lives will be saved by flooding the streets with more guns?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "You would -- just to clarify, you want everyone in Oklahoma to have the right to just carry guns, anywhere they wish, right?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I think that the more people that carry guns, yes.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "... but therefore, you would like more guns on the streets?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Do you really believe that, Senator?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "No, because I'm not going to force anyone to violate what they don't want to do.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "You really believe that -- presumably of the ultimate, your utopia is that every American wanders around the streets of America armed and that makes it safer?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "No, I would not.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Would you support an assault weapons back?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I would not support any of the -- the propositions that they have presented or that you have presented, but you are more than willing to present those solutions as a constitutional amendment just to propose them as a law or as an executive order will not work.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Would you support universal background checks?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Because the constitution has currently stated that's currently written says, \"The right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed.\"", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What is your argument against knowing whether somebody about to buy gun is mentally insane and can be proven to be mentally insane or is a criminal or has a criminal record, why would you not want to know that?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "If you want to amend and change the constitution, there's a way to do that and it's through the amendment process.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Even if you're mentally insane or criminal?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "What we need to address the mental health first.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "But how do you -- how do you do -- have you been check if they're mentally insane?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, if you want to talk about mental health issues, I mean, and if you think that the government is somehow going to protect American citizens against mental health, our government has dropped the ball even on our troops...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "How do you tackle that if you don't even want to check if they're mentally insane?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "You don't want to have any background checks on guns or whatsoever, right?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "We are innocent until proven guilty in America.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Is your constitutional God-given right to not have any checks?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Mental health is the root of the problem...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Well, you're very concerned about mental health being a problem and not the gun, right?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "First of all, that's not what I said Piers.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Now, explain to me why that in itself is not completely insane?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "... I was saying that...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "... in regards to mental health...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "What is?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I can answer that one...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "What is the number one contributor factor of gun violence?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "The floor is yours senator.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Now, if you want I can answer the previous question or this last three that you thrown out at me?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "AHM: ... in this instance, so what's the next solution?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Well, like I said, I mean, if you want things to be...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What else could it possibly be?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "It is a sin nature in mankind.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "What is the key contributing factor to gun violence and gun death in America if it's not guns or mental health issues?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Because then law abiding citizens, good guys would be able protect themselves from bad guys.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Yes, how would that be an answer?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Well, I think assault weapons are good stuff.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Well, I realized that you have also mentioned in your book and then many writings that you want to ban assault weapons in America but not handguns, is that correct?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I'm going to find a gun's full stop (ph).", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "But you do want to ban handguns as well?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Well, on this time, more people want guns for hunting.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "And shotguns?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I believe that his son has his right to life and it's very sad news (ph) that there was not somebody there to protect his son.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Do you agree with him that his son's right to his life should supersede the right of an American to own a military style assault weapon of high capacity magazine?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "See, the problem...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Is his son's right to life more important than an American's right to own a military style assault weapon and high capacity of magazine as he said?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "The problem here Piers is that...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "You don't understand what rights are, you, yourself said, just a moment ago, that you're fine with people having...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Would you agree with him or not?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I believe that both of them should and could co-exist.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Do you agree with him or do you not agree with him?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "In other word, you get a Second Amendment?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "A well-regulated militia being necessary to the security of a free state.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Gun?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "So, you would say that's it would be fine for militia members and maybe military police to own AK-47...", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Where does the well-regulated militia part come into this?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well -- just to clarify again, you are fine with militia members owning AR-15s.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What part of that constitutes for the founding fathers in your constitution describes as a well-regulated militia?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I believe so.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Did you think that most Oklahomans agree with you?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Crabtree.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it was tough.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "And what kind of adversity do you think he has overcome to get where he has?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Well, you know, now that I'm a parent, myself, I totally understand everything that our parent put us through, you know.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Talk me through some of those rules and why you think perhaps, at the heart of all these is parental responsibility?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Well my impression was -- the first thing I said to my brother I said, \"Bro I love you man.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "But what was your impression when you heard him react like that?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Good evening Piers.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Ben, how are you?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I believe you're right about that, Piers.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "I don't think there's ever been such an incredible fast speed domination of the American music chart in history, is it?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Let's just say, a cacophony noise, isn't it?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Yes it is.", "docId": "140127pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "Is this is the same were in Miller?", "qSentId": 635}]